A Guide to the Papers of the Dean of Students,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Dean of Students
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
18/2/1.072
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Formerly accessioned as MSS 6852, these papers were transferred to the University of Virginia Archives in May 2007.
Scope and Content
This collection includes the letters, memoranda and papers of B. F. D. Runk, first as Registrar and later as Dean of Students of the University of Virginia (1959-). Includes information on University of Virginia Director of Student Affairs and Admissions, University of Virginia Dean of Admissions, and University of Virginia Director of College Admissions. The papers consist of ca. 24,675 items (73 boxes, ca. 30.5 linear feet).
After J.H. Newman retired as Dean of Students in 1949 he was not replaced. Instead the duties of the Dean of Students were passed on to R.R. Fletcher as the Director of Student Affairs and Admissions until ca. 1955 when they were passed on to B.F.D. Runk, Dean of the University. This collection includes the papers of B.F.D. Runk as Registrar and as Dean of the University; R.R. Fletcher Dean of Admissions and Director of Student Affairs; R.C. Bice Dean of Admissions; J.E. Kinard Dean of Admissions; M.B. Perry Dean of Admissions; Vincent Shea Comptroller; J.H. Newman Dean of Students.
Boxes 16-38 contain detailed information on the fraternities of the University for the years 1946-1961 including rosters and scholarship ratings.
A relevant manuscript (MSS 6519) that was mentioned in the collection was added.
Arrangement
The folders are arranged alphabetically by subject.
Contents List
- Academic Legislation, Committee on, 1951 August-1953 November (Box-folder 1:1)
- Accommodations for Student Dates, 1953 February-1954 November (Box-folder 1:2)
- Administrative Committees, 1952 October-1960 September (Box-folder 1:3)
- Admissions, 1960 September-1961 August (Box-folder 1:4)
- Admissions, 1959 September-1960 November (Box-folder 1:5)
- Admissions, 1958 September-1959 August (Box-folder 1:6)
- Admissions, 1958 January-May (Box-folder 1:7)
- Admissions, 1957 February-July (Box-folder 1:8)
- Admissions, 1956 January-August (Box-folder 1:9)
- Admissions, 1954 October-1956 September (Box-folder 1:10)
- Admissions, 1953 September-1954 August (Box-folder 1:11)
- Admissions, 1952 December-1953 August (Box-folder 2:1)
- Admissions, 1952 September-November (Box-folder 2:2)
- Admissions, 1952 February-August (Box-folder 2:3)
- Admissions, 1951 September-1952 January (Box-folder 2:4)
- Admissions, 1939-1951 (Box-folder 2:5)
- Admissions Denials Reports from Deans, 1959 October-December (Box-folder 3:1)
- Alabama, State Teachers College, 1957 January-February (Box-folder 3:2)
- Alderman Library, 1953 January-1957 May (Box-folder 3:3)
- Alumni Association, 1959 July-1960 June (Box-folder 3:4)
- Alumni Association & Miscellaneous, 1957 December-1960 May (Box-folder 3:5)
- Alumni Concessions, 1950 December-1954 April (Box-folder 3:6)
- Alumni-Norfolk Trip, 1959 October-1961 January (Box-folder 3:7)
- American Association of Collegiate Registrars & Admissions Officers, 1959 February-1960 April (Box-folder 3:8)
- American Association of Collegiate Registrars & Admissions Officers, 1950 March-1952 November (Box-folder 3:9)
- American Institute of Architects, 1952 October, 1954 October (Box-folder 3:10)
- American Personnel & Guidance Association, 1952 December-1956 March (Box-folder 3:11)
- Amherst College, 1957 February (Box-folder 3:12)
- Architecture, School of, 1950 January-1958 September (Box-folder 3:13)
- Arnold Air Society, 1955 March-November (Box-folder 3:14)
- Asiatic Flu Epidemic, 1957 September-October (Box-folder 3:15)
- Athletics, Department of, 1958 March-1961 May (Box-folder 4:1)
- Atlanta Trip, 1960 January-February (Box-folder 4:2)
- Austin College, 1956 August (Box-folder 4:3)
- Bad Check Committee, 1950 June-1956 February (Box-folder 4:4)
- Band-Card Trick Plans, 1952 September-December (Box-folder 4:5)
- Beer Deliveries, 1952 October-1953 October (Box-folder 4:6)
- Bicycle Requests, 1960 April-July (Box-folder 4:7)
- Bolivian Seminar, 1958 October-1961 June (Box-folder 4:8)
- Bonding of Students, 1952 December-1953 February (Box-folder 4:9)
- Bridge to Freedom Organization, 1960 April-May (Box-folder 4:10)
- Buildings & Grounds, 1958 May-1961 June (Box-folder 4:11)
- Buildings & Grounds, 1947 September-1957 May (Box-folder 4:12)
- Bursar, 1953 July-1960 September (Box-folder 4:13)
- Bursar, 1950 June-1953 February (Box-folder 4:14)
- Calconon Fraternity, 1948 January-May (Box-folder 4:15)
- Calendar and Scheduling Committee, 1956 October-1960 May (Box-folder 4:16)
- Calendar Reservations, 1952 June-1957 August (Box-folder 5:1)
- California, University of, 1951 July-1956 June (Box-folder 5:2)
- Camera Club, 1953 November-1955 April (Box-folder 5:3)
- Car Permissions "A-Y," 1959 September-1960 February (Box-folder 5:4)
- Car Permits "A-F," 1961 September-1962 June (Box-folder 5:5)
- Car Permits "G-N," 1961 September-1962 June (Box-folder 5:6)
- Car Permits "P-Z," 1961 September-1962 June (Box-folder 5:7)
- Car Permits "A-K," 1960 September-1961 April (Box-folder 5:8)
- Car Permits "L-Z," 1960 September-1961 April (Box-folder 6:1)
- Car Permits to First Year Students "A-L," 1951 July-1955 September (Box-folder 6:2)
- Car Permits to First Year Students "M-Y," 1951 July-1955 September (Box-folder 6:3)
- Car Restrictions: Violations, Withdrawal of Privileges, 1954 September-1955 July (Box-folder 6:4)
- Car Study: Committee on Undergraduates, 1955 June-1959 May, n.d. (Box-folder 6:5)
- Carroll's Tea Room, 1951 April-1956 March (Box-folder 6:6)
- Carruthers Party, 1961 October-December (Box-folder 6:7)
- Catalogues, 1950 January-1955 October (Box-folder 6:8)
- Catalogue Revision, 1960 January-1961 March (Box-folder 6:9)
- The Cavalier Daily, 1960 January-1961 May (Box-folder 6:10)
- Cave Club, 1959 October-1960 February (Box-folder 6:11)
- Chapel Committee, 1953 March-1955 November (Box-folder 7:1)
- Chapel Reservations, 1956 May-1958 June (Box-folder 7:2)
- Chapel Reservations, 1954 August-1956 April (Box-folder 7:3)
- Chapel Reservations, 1952 May-1954 July (Box-folder 7:4)
- Chaperone System, 1951 March-1956 April (Box-folder 7:5)
- Charitable Solicitation Programs, 1952 November-December (Box-folder 7:6)
- Chicago, University of, 1952 January, 1955 May (Box-folder 7:7)
- Church Interests (Local), 1951 March-1956 October (Box-folder 7:8)
- Circle K Club, 1957 September-November (Box-folder 7:9)
- Clinch Valley College of the University of Virginia, 1959 June-1961 May (Box-folder 7:10)
- College of Arts & Sciences, 1960 January-1961 August (Box-folder 8:1)
- College of Arts & Sciences, 1955 June-1959 December (Box-folder 8:2)
- College of Arts & Sciences, 1954 January-1955 May (Box-folder 8:3)
- College of Arts & Sciences, 1950 February-1953 December, n.d. (Box-folder 8:4)
- College Quotas, Committee on, 1955 December-1956 April (Box-folder 8:5)
- Columbia University, 1952 December-1953 November (Box-folder 8:6)
- Community Chest Drive, 1957-1958 December (Box-folder 8:7)
- Comptroller, 1953 January-1961 July (Box-folder 9:1)
- Conferences, Committee on, 1954 August-1955 July (Box-folder 9:2)
- Co-Op Bookstore, 1959 October (Box-folder 9:3)
- Copeley Hill Traffic, 1959 July-August (Box-folder 9:4)
- Corks and Curls, 1955 November-1961 August (Box-folder 9:5)
- Corks and Curls, 1950 December-1955 June (Box-folder 9:6)
- Cornell University, 1952 November-1954 October (Box-folder 9:7)
- Counselors-General, 1950 December-1959 March (Box-folder 9:8)
- Counselors-Halls, 1953 June-1955 May (Box-folder 9:9)
- Counselors-Halls, 1950 September-1953 May (Box-folder 9:10)
- Counselors-Halls- Medical, 1951 May-1955 May (Box-folder 9:11)
- Counselors-Houses, 1954 May-1956 February (Box-folder 9:12)
- Counselors- Houses, 1953 January-1954 February (Box-folder 10:1)
- Counselors- Houses, 1951 January-1952 December (Box-folder 10:2)
- Counselors-Houses, 1950 January-December, n.d. (Box-folder 10:3)
- Counselors & the Counseling System, 1959 October-1961 May (Box-folder 10:4)
- Counselors & the Counseling System, 1957 September-1959 September (Box-folder 10:5)
- Course Evaluation Program, 1953 October-1954 April (Box-folder 10:6)
- Dabney House, 1951 November-1952 March (Box-folder 10:7)
- Dance Societies, 1954 January-1960 May (Box-folder 10:8)
- Dance Societies, 1950 October-1953 December (Box-folder 10:9)
- Danforth Foundation, 1951 March-1955 May (Box-folder 11:1)
- Dartmouth College, 1951 August (Box-folder 11:2)
- Davidson College, 1954 June-July (Box-folder 11:3)
- Dean of the University- General Correspondence, 1961 November-1962 May (Box-folder 11:4)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1961 August-October (Box-folder 11:5)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1961 May-July (Box-folder 11:6)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1961 January-April (Box-folder 11:7)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1960 August-December (Box-folder 11:8)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1960 April-July (Box-folder 12:1)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1960 February-March (Box-folder 12:2)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1959 October-1960 January (Box-folder 12:3)
- Dean of the University- General Correspondence, 1959 June-September (Box-folder 12:4)
- Dean of the University- General Correspondence, 1959 April-May (Box-folder 12:5)
- Dean of the University-General Correspondence, 1959 February-March, n.d. (Box-folder 13:1)
- Deans' Committee on Student Affairs, 1950 October-1951 November (Box-folder 13:2)
- Deans' List of Distinguished Students, 1960 March-1961 June (Box-folder 13:3)
- Delaware, University of, 1953 July-1955 January (Box-folder 13:4)
- Dell, The, 1958 August (Box-folder 13:5)
- Delta Sigma Phi, 1959 October-November (Box-folder 13:6)
- Duke University, 1956 April-May (Box-folder 13:7)
- Easters, 1953 March-October (Box-folder 13:8)
- E.F. Blake Memorial Award Committee, 1953 March-October (Box-folder 13:9)
- Education, School of, 1952 December-1957 May (Box-folder 13:10)
- Education, School of, 1950 February-1952 November (Box-folder 13:11)
- Engineering, School of, 1953 January-1957 February (Box-folder 14:1)
- Engineering, School of, 1949 November-1952 December (Box-folder 14:2)
- Engineers' Club 1950 October-1961 August (Box-folder 14:3)
- Entering Class-By Schools, 1949 October-[1950] (Box-folder 14:4)
- Equipment, 1957 December-1962 May, n.d. (Box-folder 14:5)
- Faculty, 1951 January-1956 June (Box-folder 14:6)
- Faculty, 1942 December, 1948 September-1950 December, n.d. (Box-folder 14:7)
- Film and Film Strips, 1950 March-1953 November (Box-folder 15:1)
- Firearms, 1950 November-1951 September (Box-folder 15:2)
- Fire Regulations & Inspections, 1955 December-1957 October (Box-folder 15:3)
- Fires, 1951 February-1952 June (Box-folder 15:4)
- First Year Forum, 1952 April (Box-folder 15:5)
- Florida State University, 1953 July-1954 November (Box-folder 15:6)
- Food Services, 1950 November-1956 February (Box-folder 15:7)
- Founder's Day 1961 March- April (Box-folder 15:8)
- Founder's Day 1960 March-April (Box-folder 15:9)
- Fraternities-3-3-3 Committee, 1955 July-1956 September (Box-folder 15:10)
- Fraternities-3-3-3 Committee, 1955 January- July (Box-folder 16:1)
- Fraternities-Advisors Association, 1947 November-1960 November (Box-folder 16:2)
- Fraternities Agreements A-Z, 1958 January-March (Box-folder 16:3)
- Fraternities-Background Data, 1942-1955 March, n.d. (Box-folder 16:4)
- Fraternities, Committee on, 1960 June-1961 August (Box-folder 16:5)
- Fraternities, Committee on, 1959 July - 1960 May (Box-folder 16:6)
- Fraternities, Committee on, 1958 May-1959 May (Box-folder 17:1)
- Fraternities, Committee on, 1956 September-1958 April (Box-folder 17:2)
- Fraternities, Committee on, 1955 January- September (Box-folder 17:3)
- Fraternities, Committee on, 1942 November-1954 December (Box-folder 17:4)
- Fraternities, Committee on: Hostess Applications, 1954 September-1957 July (Box-folder 17:5)
- Fraternities, Committee on: Hostesses, 1955 September-1958 June (Box-folder 17:6)
- Fraternities, Committee on: Scholarship Study, 1959 July-December (Box-folder 18:1)
- Fraternities-Cross Fraternity Scholarship, 1954 November-1957 May (Box-folder 18:2)
- Fraternities-Dining Room Managers Group, 1956 April (Box-folder 18:3)
- Fraternities Distributions, 1954 May-October; ca. 1950 (Box-folder 18:4)
  Fraternities-Drawing of University of Virginia grounds with the locations of 32 fraternities noted (oversize).
- Fraternities-Hazing, 1956 February-1959 November (Box-folder 18:5)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Alpha Omega Alpha-Medical, 1959 (Box-folder 18:6)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Beta Beta Beta-Biology, 1955 May, 1956 January (Box-folder 18:7)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Beta Gamma Sigma-Commerce, 1959 April (Box-folder 18:8)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Delta Sigma Rho-Forensics, 1954 November (Box-folder 18:9)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Delta Theta Phi-Law, 1955 March (Box-folder 18:10)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Gamma Theta Upsilon-Geography, 1952 May (Box-folder 18:11)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Kappa Delta Pi-Education, 1954 October (Box-folder 18:12)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Omicron Delta Kappa-Leadership, 1957 May-1961 July (Box-folder 18:13)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Omicron Delta Kappa-Leadership, 1954 February-1957 April (Box-folder 18:14)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Omicron Delta Kappa-Leadership, 1949 June-1954 January, n.d. (Box-folder 18:15)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Phi Beta Kappa-Undergraduate, 1954 November-1958 January (Box-folder 19:1)
- Fraternities, Honorary- Pi Delta Epsilon-Journalism, 1956 February-1960 February (Box-folder 19:2)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Sigma Gamma Epsilon-Geology, 1957 October (Box-folder 19:3)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Sigma Xi-Scientific Research, n.d. (Box-folder 19:4)
- Fraternities, Honorary-Tau Beta Pi-Engineering, n.d. (Box-folder 19:5)
- Fraternities Hostesses: New Names, 1956 June-1960 March (Box-folder 19:6)
- Fraternities Hostesses: Permanent, 1959 May-1961 August (Box-folder 19:7)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1960 April-1961 September (Box-folder 19:8)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1958 September-1960 March (Box-folder 19:9)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1956 October-1958 August (Box-folder 19:10)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1955 September-1956 September (Box-folder 20:1)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1953 February-1955 May (Box-folder 20:2)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1951 March-1953 January (Box-folder 20:3)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council, 1946 April-1951 February (Box-folder 20:4)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Council: Medical, 1953 September-1956 May (Box-folder 20:5)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Representatives, 1951 February-1956 February (Box-folder 20:6)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Research & Advisory Council, 1953 July-1957 April (Box-folder 20:7)
- Fraternities-Interfraternity Scholarship Awards, 1951 April-May (Box-folder 20:8)
- Fraternities Lists-Officers, Hostesses, Advisers, 1960 September-October (Box-folder 20:9)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1961-1962 Session, 1961 October (Box-folder 21:1)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1961-1962 Session, 1961 April-September (Box-folder 21:2)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z, 1961 April-June (Box-folder 21:3)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1960-1961 Session, 1960 September-1961 February (Box-folder 21:4)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1959-1960 Session, 1959 December-1960 June (Box-folder 21:5)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1954-1955 Session, 1955 April-May (Box-folder 21:6)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1954-1955 Session, 1954 October-December (Box-folder 21:7)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1953-1954 Session, 1954 January-February (Box-folder 22:1)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z 1951-1952 Session, 1951 September-1952 February (Box-folder 22:2)
- Fraternities-Membership Rosters A-Z, [1949 -1952?] (Box-folder 22:3)
- Fraternities-Miscellaneous, 1956 August-1960 May (Box-folder 22:4)
- Fraternities-Miscellaneous, 1946 July-1956 May (Box-folder 22:5)
- Fraternities-National Interfraternity Conference, 1956 October-1960 August (Box-folder 22:6)
- Fraternities-National Interfraternity Conference, 1955 April-1956 September (Box-folder 22:7)
- Fraternities-National Interfraternity Conference, 1950 October-1954 December (Box-folder 23:1)
- Fraternities-National Scholarship Association, 1958 August-1960 June (Box-folder 23:2)
- Fraternities-New Chapters, 1953 May-1959 October (Box-folder 23:3)
- Fraternities-Officers A-Z, 1961 September-October (Box-folder 23:4)
- Fraternities-Pledge Grades, 1951 June (Box-folder 23:5)
- Fraternities, Professional-Alpha Chi Sigma-Chemistry, 1955 October, 1956 April (Box-folder 23:6)
- Fraternities, Professional-Alpha Kappa Psi-Business, 1952 December, 1959 January (Box-folder 23:7)
- Fraternities, Professional-Alpha Rho Chi-Architecture, 1952 October, 1955 May (Box-folder 23:8)
- Fraternities, Professional-Delta Sigma Pi-Commerce, n.d. (Box-folder 23:9)
- Fraternities, Professional-Lambda Pi-Political, 1953 June-1956 April (Box-folder 23:10)
- Fraternities, Professional-Nu Sigma Nu-Medical, 1948 January-1954 April (Box-folder 23:11)
- Fraternities, Professional-Phi Beta Pi-Medical, 1948 May-1955 June (Box-folder 23:12)
- Fraternities, Professional-Phi Chi-Medical, 1948 January-1956 April (Box-folder 23:13)
- Fraternities, Professional-Phi Delta Kappa-Education, 1948 July-1955 July (Box-folder 23:14)
- Fraternities, Professional-Phi Delta Phi-Law, 1953 April-1960 April (Box-folder 23:15)
- Fraternities, Professional-Phi Lambda Kappa-Medical, 1948 January-May (Box-folder 23:16)
- Fraternities, Professional-Theta Tau-Engineering, 1953 May-1960 May (Box-folder 23:17)
- Fraternities Rushing, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 23:18)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Ratings, 1947-1957 April (Box-folder 24:1)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1960-1961 Session, 1960 September-1961 December (Box-folder 24:2)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1959-1960 Session, 1959 November-December (Box-folder 24:3)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1958-1959 Session, 1959 March-July (Box-folder 24:4)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1958-1959 Session, 1958 October-1959 February (Box-folder 24:5)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1957-1958 Session, 1958 February-May (Box-folder 24:6)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1956-1957 Session, 1957 February-September (Box-folder 24:7)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1956-1957 Session, 1956 September-December (Box-folder 25:1)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1955-1956 Session, 1956 April-May (Box-folder 25:2)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1955-1956 Session, 1955 October-November (Box-folder 25:3)
- Fraternities-Scholarship Rosters A-Z 1953-1954 Session, 1954 January (Box-folder 25:4)
- Fraternities, Service-Alpha Phi Omega, 1949 October-1951 April (Box-folder 25:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1956 November-1961 April (Box-folder 25:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1944 June, 1953 January-1956 October (Box-folder 25:7)
- Fraternities, Social-Alpha Tau Omega, 1958 February-1961 August (Box-folder 25:8)
- Fraternities, Social-Alpha Tau Omega, 1946 May-1957 December (Box-folder 25:9)
- Fraternities, Social-Beta Theta Pi, 1958 February-1961 May (Box-folder 26:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Beta Theta Pi, 1946 April-1957 December (Box-folder 26:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Phi, 1959 March-1961 June (Box-folder 26:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Phi, 1956 September-1959 February (Box-folder 26:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Phi, 1946 May-1956 August (Box-folder 26:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Psi, 1959 April-1961 August (Box-folder 27:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Psi, 1956 October-1959 February (Box-folder 27:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Psi, 1949 February-1956 September (Box-folder 27:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Chi Psi-Lectures, 1955 April-May (Box-folder 27:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1957 October-1961 July (Box-folder 27:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1946 September-1957 May (Box-folder 27:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Sigma Phi, 1956 April (Box-folder 27:7)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Tau Delta (Serpentine Club), 1946 April-November, 1949 September (Box-folder 27:8)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Upsilon, 1959 March-1961 May (Box-folder 28:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Upsilon, 1956 March-1959 February (Box-folder 28:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Delta Upsilon, 1947 January-1956 February (Box-folder 28:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Kappa Alpha, 1957 December-1961 April (Box-folder 28:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Kappa Alpha, 1945 October-1957 October (Box-folder 28:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Kappa Sigma, 1959 May-1961 July (Box-folder 28:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Kappa Sigma, 1956 March-1959 April (Box-folder 29:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Kappa Sigma, 1946 August-1956 February (Box-folder 29:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Kappa Sigma Kappa, 1953 June (Box-folder 29:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Alpha, 1946 August (Box-folder 29:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Delta Theta, 1957 October-1961 May (Box-folder 29:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Delta Theta, 1946 June-1957 June (Box-folder 29:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Epsilon Pi, 1957 May-1961 August (Box-folder 29:7)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Epsilon Pi, 1947 April-1957 May (Box-folder 29:8)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Gamma Delta, 1958 November-1961 August (Box-folder 30:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Gamma Delta, 1955 January-1958 October (Box-folder 30:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Gamma Delta, 1946 August-1954 December (Box-folder 30:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Kappa Psi, 1956 April-1961 May (Box-folder 30:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Kappa Psi, 1946 May-1956 March (Box-folder 30:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Kappa Sigma, 1958 April-1961 August (Box-folder 30:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Kappa Sigma, 1953 October-1958 March (Box-folder 31:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Kappa Sigma, 1946 June-1953 August (Box-folder 31:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Sigma Kappa, 1958 January-1961 June (Box-folder 31:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Phi Sigma Kappa (Column Club), 1949 April-1957 December (Box-folder 31:4)
- Fraternities, Social -Pi Kappa Alpha, 1959 October- 1961 April (Box-folder 31:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Pi Kappa Alpha, 1946 September-1959 May (Box-folder 31:6)
- Fraternities, Social - Pi Kappa Phi (Alpha Mu Club), 1960 April-1961 August (Box-folder 32:1)
  Includes MSS 6519.
- Fraternities, Social-Pi Kappa Phi (Alpha Mu Club), 1959 March-1960 March (Box-folder 32:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1958 March-1961 August (Box-folder 32:3)
- Fraternities, Social -Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1952 March-1958 February (Box-folder 32:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Alpha Epsilon (COPIES?), 1946 May-1951 October (Box-folder 32:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Chi, 1957 December-1961 June (Box-folder 32:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Chi, 1946 March-1957 November (Box-folder 33:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Nu, 1957 November-1961 June (Box-folder 33:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Nu, 1953 January-1957 October (Box-folder 33:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Nu, 1946 July-1953 December (Box-folder 33:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi, 1958 November-1961 August (Box-folder 33:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi, 1956 December-1958 October (Box-folder 34:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi (Serpentine Club), 1950 April-1956 November (Box-folder 34:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1958 September-1961 August (Box-folder 34:3)